[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "What happens next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "It is over in the sense that whatever we're talking about, we're talking about a period of transition until you get to elections.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak", "Omar Suleiman"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you see anybody emerging, Anderson, tonight as a potential candidate to take over for Mubarak?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I mean, Mubarak has appointed a vice president, Omar Suleiman, who is head of his intelligence -- who's been his intelligence chief for years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Describe what you've seen and what you think is going to happen next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "People are enormously energized by the fact that they've found their voice, for the first time in 30 years, and they're not placated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "I mean, would you think from what you just said that Mubarak may be lucky to survive even the week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I sure wouldn't want to make a prediction about how long Mubarak is going to last, but what I do think is that right now, he has become an impediment to stability in Egypt.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "And are you picking up any sense of anti-Americanism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's passing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Mr. Blair, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Very well, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Blair"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "It's been a while.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "These are pretty extraordinary times, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "They are extraordinary times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "And in particular, I think the key challenge for us, really, is how do we help partner this process of change and help manage it in such a way that what comes out of it is open-minded, fair, democratic government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "WP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Nobody seems quite sure what to say about President Mubarak.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Where do you stand on him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Well, where you stand on him depends on whether you've worked with him from the outside or on the inside.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, I think it's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Presumably, you would be critical of that kind of behavior by any government, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Of course I don't want to see that in any government.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "You weren't proud before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "And now you're proud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "How do you feel being a peace envoy in an area of the world where a lot of Arabs don't trust you and don't like you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, some do, some don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Isn't it a better way to secure regime change than declaring war on countries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "It's a much better way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain", "America"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "How do you think this is all going to play out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, I think it all plays out depending on whether, as I say, the modernizing forces, the people who want, you know, the types of things we take for granted in Britain and America, and whether they are the people that would succeed those governments, or whether the very strong Islamist movements wouldn't rather take control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "Isn't that the fear for all these -- all these governments in the Middle East now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ":", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "Yes, but that in a sense is a healthy thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Finally, Mr. Blair, do you believe in your position as Middle East peace envoy, do you believe that peace is now more or less likely the way things stand today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "It's extremely difficult to tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Blair"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Is that position tenable, do you think, given the reaction on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Well, that's something with he and his government and the people are going to have to decide.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "POS", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ":"], "qSentId": 271, "question": "If you'd been asked, as Vice President Biden was asked, is he a dictator, what would you have said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I'm not in the vice president's shoes, so I'm not going to --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Let me ask you as Governor Romney, is he a dictator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "He's the leader of his country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "They see him as a dictator and they want someone in America to actually stand up for them, don't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, they want to know that the America people stand with the voices of freedom and democracy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "CD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "hasn't that game now run its course?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "Well, there's always been a bit of a potential conflict and a balance between two of our interests in foreign policy; one being that we support values and principles they are consistent with our own.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "But what was your take on what was going on there when you were there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, it was just a few weeks ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia", "Middle East"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Were you surprised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, what happened in Tunisia is having a seismic effect on what's happening throughout the Middle East.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Yes or no, are you going to run for the presidency again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I don't have an answer for you yet, because there are a lot of things you have to consider before you make that final decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "Am I right in thinking you know the answer, you just don't want to give it to me yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "No, I don't have a 100 percent answer ready to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Does you and your position now emerge as the savior, if you like, of all this polarizing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "You know, I'm not somebody who can analyze for you the politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "What do you believe about Sarah Palin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I believe she's an extraordinarily powerful and effective voice in our party, that she has generated a great deal of support and attention, that she'd be great in a primary process.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Could you beat her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I don't know the answer to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Does your wife know the answer to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "She probably does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "She thinks you can beat everyone, doesn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure she knows whether I can win or lose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", ":", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "I mean, you're pretty perfect, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Well, I think people would -- particularly my family, would disagree with that conclusion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "Do you still stand by every word of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Do you think it's going to be a potential problem if you run, your faith?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Once again, I can't judge the politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "How do you respond to that charge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "OMNEY: Well, a lot of things are charged in politics, some accurate, some not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Most important thing to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I would reverse all of the policies that have made America one of the least friendly places to start new businesses and to grow business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "And can you come back maybe when you've got a bit more to say about your decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Rob, what's it like there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Piers, the most intense part of the storm is happening right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Have you seen that before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I lost ISP, so I assume we're done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110201pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "When did the shooting happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "a couple of hours ago, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]